Make a note of it!

Stickies lets you keep notes (like these) on your desktop. Use a Stickies note to jot down reminders, lists, or other information. You can also use notes to store frequently used text or graphics.

• To close this note, click the close button.

• To collapse this note, double click the title bar.

Your current notes appear when you open Stickies.

It’s easy to customize your notes.

Make your notes stand out and get noticed.

• Format text using different fonts and font sizes
• Add emphasis with bold and italic text styles or color.
• Include graphics  . 

Stickies has lots of other great features, including a spell checker, import and export features, and other ways to arrange and customize your notes. Plus, you’ll find a “Make New Sticky Note” service in many applications.

Look in Help to find out more about using Stickies.


*** When using yabai ***
Keep stickies in minimized mode when started yabai otherwise they will take up their own area in the window like a standard app

*** When using with stage manager ***
When using stickies with stage manager it will accidentally pull them into the side bar in stage manager so don't use stage manager with stickies until apple fixes it with an update.
